(THE YARNS)
If Sky wasn't the one fighting the prey,
it could be none other than identical twins.
Even Sky can't tell herself apart from her twin.
I think Fah came to check the documents to see if the victims she killed really had killer genes...
to ensure that she didn't mess up.
Now it turns out that the one who doesn't have killer genes,
is actually a murderer, killing ones with killer genes.
We need to go back to the root of the matter.
I'll help you send you far away.
Die! Die!
They're dead
They died again!
Again!
Died again!
Sky, Sky!
Sky, Sky.
Is this here, Sky?
- I don't know
- Did you find it, Inspector?
No, Sergeant, please search urgently.
- I do not know
- Yes, sir.
Where on earth have you been?
Huh? Why are you home so late?
Didn't I tell you that there's news
about a murder out there lately.
Fah?
Damn you Fah, what kind of pranks
have you been up to again?
Fah,
Why are you yelling so loudly, Grandma?
You will wake up mom.
How can I not be loud and noisy?
Just look at you.
What have you been doing, Fah?
I am just doing my duty to show gratitude to my mother as everyone has taught me.
'Make sure to show gratitude.'
Does it mean that every time Sky just goes outside...
not knowing where to go?
It seems that way.
Then how does she know her way to school?
It must be a place that Sky is familiar
with and has been to. That's why
And then, after Sky returned home
She sat knitting this pattern all day.
She really put her heart into knitting
and didn't say a word.
Seems very much like being in a trance.
If the next corpse really exists
and it's similar to her behaviour,
the body is hanging down,
, with many cuts that the prey is bled out completely.
What's up, Nawin?
You found the ninth body?
Okay, I'll hurry and go.
Sergeant, you don't have to go.
Just wait here and be on standby.
Yes, sir.
Who is the deceased?
I'm checking it out, Inspector.
Mr. Phakhin?
Lan.
Don't tell me this is...
the director of the Department of Scientific
and Crime Registration.
Mark, come with me.
Thanks. Lieutenant, here is...
the yarn we found in the scene.
It was heavily criticized...
that what the reasons behind the culprit's action...
are to oppose the law that controls the behavior of those with killer genes.
The person who proposes
this law is Dr. Chonlathorn Traikanon,
one of the prime minister's running candidates...
in the upcoming election which is in two weeks.
Now society is starting to question this issue,
meanwhile, Dr. Chonlathorn...
still has no sign that he will show up
and talk about this issue.
They are attacking me directly.
Are you sure this isn't the work of the opposing party?
Why is the media focusing on me alone?
Definitely not their move, sir.
No one dares to support this murderer.
Because if the matter gets out,
the party will be dissolved,
and revoked for another ten years
Plus, there are criminal penalties.
No one would dare do it.
And who is it?
Who would have the guts to do it?
Whatever you have to say, just say it.
Sir,
I am not inciting Mr.Lan and you to fight.
I know that Mr.Lan has found out...
who the murderer is.
The reason why it isn't announced
is because he is protecting someone.
Someone, you're saying?
Do you remember the autistic child
who was the suspect last time?
But that child is not the murderer.
No, but she's the killer's twin.
Are they twins?
I got confirmation from the forensic lab results.
The murderer is that girl's identical twin.
They were raised separately,
and the murderer took advantage of looking alike with her...
disguised herself, stole the genetic results...
and exposed it on social media.
Release this kid's photo to press,
set a reward of five million baht for the capture,
and don't let anyone know that it was our work.
Yes, sir.
Hey,
hey.
Do you think that's her?
Exactly right.
- It's the same person.
- Yes, definitely.
Have it on the record!
How could anyone let a murderer roam around like this?
Take her picture.
Excuse me. Excuse me! What are you doing?
Excuse me, what do you think you are doing?
What are you doing here?
We're taking a video and report it to the police.
She is that serial killer, don't you know?
-What do you mean by a murderer?
-Don't you know?
Look, her pictures are all over social media.
This person is not a murderer. She is not a murderer.
- Which one is the culprit?
- Officer, officer, please.
I am also a police officer.
Here is my badge, Lieutenant.
- It's all a misunderstanding.
- Hello, Inspector.
Please get me out of here first. I'll explain it to you later.
Yes, Sergeant, please keep the people out.
Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
-This way, sir.
Come on, Sky.
Was it you who ordered the bounty announcement, father?
I should be the one asking you,
is it my duty to make that announcement?
But doing that isn't right, father.
In this case,
The killer has an identical twin.
Revealing the image like that,
the other twin who is innocent,
will affect her way of living.
Your duty
is to capture that damn murderer.
As for the matter of rights,
let's leave it to the human rights activists.
Police duties
are to preserve the rights of the people.
Even if that person has committed a crime,
they have the right to prove themself.
The person you are talking about right now...
is an autistic kid,
the twin of the psychotic killer? It seems like…
you are especially worried about her.
Father, Sky is in a lot of trouble because of your actions.
She can hardly go anywhere,
because people misunderstood her as the culprit.
So?
Why should I care about that kid?
My duty...
is to catch that psycho killer.
And for you,
Go do your job,
before I run out of patience.
You never cared about other people's feelings.
You're only immersed in achieving your own goals
That's because I'm honest with myself.
I know my purpose,
- and for whom I'm doing it for.
- Are you honest with yourself,
or are you selfish?
You used the people as an excuse,
but deep down,
all the things you have done,
it's to make up for the mistake you committed to auntie,
and the son of the deceased father.
Lan!
You are being ungrateful to me.
Father, you can call me ungrateful to push me down.
But you can't use it against other people who aren't involved.
I didn't raise you to talk back to me.
It is your duty to catch that murderer.
Prove it to me...
that I didn't waste my time raising you up.
Fah!
What on earth have you done?
I went to the market and saw your arrest
warrant all over the news.
You didn't do it, did you?
Why are you packing your clothes?
Don't tell me you really killed someone.
You already know, but you still ask? It's annoying.
You scumbag!
How could you do this?
I raised you. I never taught you to kill anyone.
Look at how you're saying.
You say it as if it is nothing.
You are as evil as your father.
I really shouldn't have kept you. I should have let you die like your brother.
Fah!
Is this the news that was announced?
Is the person in the picture really me?
It is your twin sister, isn't it?
Yes.
- You idiot!
- Mom?
Let me go!
- Let me go.
- Anna.
- Mom!
- Mom.
- Anna, Anna.
- It's me, Fah.
- Anna
- What's wrong
- Fah.
Is it you, Fah, my child?
You must take revenge on them for me, Fah.
- Take revenge for your mother, Fah.
- I'll take revenge for you. Don't worry.
You remember that.
You must take revenge for me.
Even though I didn't want you to be born as my child,
you have to take revenge for me.
Remember this!
Yes.
I am the child that you did not want.
I was born to ruin your life,
because of that one hellish beast.
You damn beast!
Where are you?
Where the hell are you, you animal?
- I'm gonna kill it. He raped me. He raped me.
- Anna, Anna.
Anna, Anna.
No, my child. No, my child.
He raped me, he raped me, mom.
He raped me.
Mom is here. Mom is here. Anna.
Anna
- He raped me. He raped me.
- Mom, mom.
It raped me. It raped me.
Darling,
it's late already.
Anna still hasn't come back yet.
I called, but she didn't answer.
You can call her later.
Maybe she is still in a meeting.
But it's not usually like this, dear.
I think we should go and get our daughter home.
Let's go.
Anna!
-Anna!
- Anna!
Baby.
What's wrong?
Who did what to you?
Mom.
Anna.
- Blood!
- Dad.
He raped me.
He raped me. He raped me.
He raped me!
Dad, Dad, help me.
Mommy is here, baby.
He raped me.
Nuan.
Take her to the doctor.
I'm going to kill him.
I'm going to fucking kill him.
My dear,
calm down.
- What's wrong, baby?
- He raped me.
He raped me, Dad, you have to save me.
- Dad and Mom are here, baby.
- Dad, you have to help me. Mom.
Mom, please help me.
We are here for you now.
Grandma, did you see that?
I was born from mom being raped.
My mother never wanted me to be born.
That's not all.
You sell my genes, grandma.
I can't choose being born.
I can't even choose to live the way I want.
Now people know I have killer genes,
I will kill all the bastards who are ruining our lives.
Fah, don't do this again.
Fah!
The autopsy results of Director Pakin's case,
shows that he was cut and bled while hanging.
A large amount of blood comes out faster than normal,
because the murderer injected a stimulant that made the heart beat faster than normal.
And does Pakin have killer genes?
But why did Fah choose to kill the director?
It doesn't match the puzzle,
and the director is not one of the people
who fake genetic results.
It's too out of the pattern.
Or is the culprit changing her plan?
Mr. Pakin is probably not Fah's first target.
It's because we've already tracked down
all the possible candidates,
so Fah changed her plan.
That means we're on the right track.
That's correct.
Now, all that's left is to see
if we can stop her from killing her last victim.
Pigpen Cipher,
Or the pigsty code,
It is to fix one-to-one character substitution encryption.
There are no changes to the format.
The method is to compare the code with the table.
Then you can decode it.
Another table?
Yes, it's very easy. The method is...
to match the symbols in the yarn
to the letters in the table.
It will result in a word.
All done.
What's that?
Is this a mystery or an insult to us?
But it could imply a real career.
Like sex workers or something like that.
If it's a curse, it's considered quite a strong curse.
If it's really that profession,
it's probably difficult because
no one would register that as their career.
This is not a profession.
So how do we know what Fah's next victim's career is?
What is the occupation?
Why do you like humming this song so much?
Every time I listen to it, it sounds so creepy.
Do you know?
Since I was a kid, man.
Adults always try to teach us to be good kids like in the song.
Said that if you do it, your life will be better.
I was stupid enough to believe them.
So, in conclusion... how is it?
Look at my life.
Look at what society does to us.
Look what my mom found
So I sang this song to remind myself.
What about those ten virtues?
It's useless to do that.
It's just a song that the elite composed,
to control the poor to be obedient.
Number one, believe in your religion.
Two, be traditional.
Three, listen to your parents and teachers.
Four, your words must be polite and gentle.
Five, must show gratitude.
Six, be sure to love working.
Wait a minute Sky, Sky.
Let me ask you something.
Why does Sky like to sing this song so much?
Sky doesn't like it,
but I hear it so often.
I've heard it so often that it's stuck in my head.
Do you hear that often, Sky?
Normally, I hardly ever hear this song anymore, except during Children's Day.
It is rarely on anymore.
But Sky really hears it regularly.
It is so strange.
It's very strange.
Fah also likes to use this song when attacking.
The last time when she killed the student,
I heard about it.
Wait a minute Sky.
Is this song about 'Good Children's 10 duties'?
Yes, it is.
'Good children must have 10 duties'.
10 things.
Fah also wants to kill 10 corpses in total.
Bingo.
The song is the key.
Yes, the song is the key.
Ornchuma.
Pakin
Got it.
Two Maintaining traditions. Maintaining traditions.
Keeping traditions, keeping traditions
Brahmin.
Traditions, traditions, I think this is it.
Next, Sky.
Stop Sky
Four, your words
must be polite and gentle.
Polite speech. Polite speech.
Is it Ya?
Ya spoke politely. She spoke very gently.
Isriya,
Public relations officer.
I think so, Sky.
Continue.
Five, must show gratitude.
Stop, Sky.
Who is holding on to gratitude?
Adhere to gratitude.
Six is about working.
Skip and continue, please, Sky.
Seven, must study hard to become an expert.
You must be diligent and persevering, don't be lazy.
Bank employee as for know of saving.
Nine, must be honest at all times with sportsmanship.
Noppachai, a boxer.
Ten.
Okay.
Now we have 2 more names
and 3 parts of the song left.
Five, must show gratitude.
Who is grateful?
Must show gratitude?
Who is holding on to gratitude?
Six, be sure to love working.
Be a person who loves to work. Love working.
Anon is a full-time employee
but works part-time at a convenience store.
I think that it's him who loved working.
Mr. Anon
Then there are two more questions left.
The ninth riddle: what is the occupation of Grandfather Som, the guardian of wealth?
The ninth corpse is because we knew the killer
and sent someone to guard the person
who could be the victim,
which was the librarian
and the museum guard.
Do we need to preserve national treasures?
Yes.
That's how Mr. Pakin was killed instead
So now we are left with the tenth victim.
With the last line of the lyrics, that is
'must show gratitude'.
It is not a profession.
I don't know either, and I'm not sure if it's right
to link the victims' occupations to the song. I don't know.
The result seems logical, in my opinion.
It might not imply directly
but they seem legit.
Sky's twin is such a psychopath,
from knitting yarn,
her killing methods and songs are all mixed up.
She is more of a genius.
Very smart.
She tricked us into exposing corruption
and her method of killing people
is based on medical knowledge.
She knows anatomy well.
It's not ordinary.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dr. Anya,
for praising Sky's twin for being smart.
Sky, I don't appreciate her being smart.
Sky thinks it is a compliment. It is indeed a compliment.
Let's discuss about the next victim's occupation possibilities.
Is it possible to include the Ruamkatanyu group?
It might be possible.
We need to get the list from Mr. Pakin
and compare it with the occupation like last time.
Lan, gratitude is a behavior. It's a behavior,
not a profession.
No matter what profession,
you can show your gratitude.
We have no way of knowing, Lan.
If I don't know, we have to know. We have to try.
Wow, this celebrity also fakes his genes?
There's a celebrity, too? Can I see that, please?
Is this person an actor? Why don't I know him?
Hey, Sergeant!
This person is very famous.
He's famous all the way to China.
He has a lot of fans.
Are you kidding? If he's that famous, why don't I know him?
He's famous among BL fans.
Oh, I see. BL actors.
Do you watch the BL series too?
I also watch some.
My sister is his fan. I know him.
Excuse me, have you ever seen the person in this picture?
- Sergeant.
- Wait a minute.
Have you ever seen the person in the picture?
That was close.
The police are everywhere at this point
and you still dared to go out?
I went out to steal some medicine
and equipment from the hospital.
So what? Almost got caught, didn't you?
Fah
I think it would be better if you ran away first.
Why should I? My plan hasn't even succeeded yet.
What the hell is your plan?
You worry about yourself first.
They can lock you in any minute. Aren't you scared?
You, you!
You'll only regret it when it's gone bad for you.
What else do people like me have to lose?
My plan will be successful in a no time.
I'm not running away anywhere.
Listen to me.
Even if you can overthrow that damn law, do you think
that you will be able to go back to living a normal life.
Your face is on every media outlet.
Eventually, if you don't get caught,
you'll have to run away for the rest of your life.
I will do it anyway.
Once I make a decision, I will do it anyway.
Shit.
Are you really after this guy?
If it's for you,
don't you think we have to go a little bigger?
I won't do it.
If I couldn't escape last time,
I'd be waiting for you in prison right now,
you damn bastard.
You believe me
this time they don't know for sure who it is.
I didn't leave any clue.
Keng, I beg you.
This will be the last time. I won't bother you again.
The reason I do it for you
is because you're my best friend.
In my life, there are only you and Lily who understand me.
Fah
Where are you, Fah, my child?
Fah, can you hear me?
Fah, damn you.
Can you hear me? Where are you?
Where have you been? Why are you locking me up?
Let me go!
Fah!
Where are you, Fah?
Let me go
Who the hell tied me up? I'm not a pig or a dog, why are you tying me up?
Oh, who's tying me up?
Oh, shit!
Let me go!
Oh, Anna!
Mom is back.
Anna, are you hungry, dear?
Anna.
Anna!
What, Grandma? Mom's missing?
Where has mom gone?
How would I know?
Grandma, calm down first.
Grandma, go look around there first.
I think Mom can't go far. I'll go help look for her.
You don't have to show your face, Fah.
Do you want to be dragged to jail by the police?
I'll find her by myself.
I'm hanging up.
Hey, wait a minute.
Where are you going?
I have to go find my mother, of course.
You wait here. Your grandma will find her soon.
Keng,
if your mother has gone missing,
will you be able to just wait?
Hey, wait, Fah.
What's your problem now?
I think you should wear this.
I'll go with you.
Give me that.
Wait a minute.
Why do you keep looking at me?
Aren't you in a hurry?
Policeman, can you please stop the car first?
Sure. Uh...
What's up, Sky?
Please wait a moment.
Auntie,
This is Sky's water.
Sky's own water.
Oh.
Auntie, the water is all over your face.
Take Sky's handkerchief and use it.
Fah.
My dear, Fah.
Fah, you come back to mommy.
- Fah, mommy misses you so much.
- Miss, miss.
- Mom misses Fah so much.
- Sky.
It's really you, Fah.
- Did you come back to your mother?
- Auntie, this is Sky.
- Fah, Fah.
- Miss, miss, let go.
My name is Sky. Sky means the space above the Earth.
Miss, release Sky.
- Miss, calm down. Miss, calm down first.
- Let me go, let me go.
Miss, miss.
- Miss, miss, calm down.
- Give me my child.
- My child.
- Miss,
- My daughter, give me my daughter.
- Miss, miss, please calm down.
- She is not your child, miss.
- My daughter, give me my daughter.
- Miss, calm down. Miss, calm down first.
- My child.
- Fah!
- Hey, what's this?
Shit, look at this.
Isn't that the police and your twin?
What should we do?
I think we should go first, you asshole.
No!
My child, my child!
What are you doing here?
Come back home, my child.
This is my baby. My baby.
My baby.
I'm sorry.
My daughter isn't in her right mind.
It's okay. Uh.
Grandma, would you like me to take you home?
She is quite strong and
I'm afraid you won't be able to handle it.
She's my baby. My baby.
Where should I take you?
Oh, that's okay.
The alley to my house is too narrow.
It's difficult for a car to go in and come back out.
I will go back with her. Go, go, my dear.
Go home, my child.
That, that...
That's my child.
- That's my baby.
- She is not your child, dear. Your child is at home.
My child is at home.
She is not your child, dear.
Let's go home, my child.
-Then let's go home, Mom. I miss my child.
- Go home, go back...
- Go, go home.
- Go home. My child is home.
Grandma.
What's up?
What is your name?
My name is Somporn.
What's up, young man?
There's nothing.
- Then, we will get going.
- My child is at home.
- Yes.
- Mom.
Let's go home.
- Go home.
- I miss my child.
I want to go see my child.
- Go, dear. Go home.
- My child is at home.
It's okay now.
Yes.
Does it hurt anywhere?
No, it doesn't hurt.
Sky was just more shocked.
Now not shocked anymore.
Yes, Sky is not shocked anymore.
I'm not shocked anymore,
but I am wondering instead.
Wondering... Wondering about what, Sky?
Why did that aunt call Sky "Fah"?
Sky, Sky, go wait for me in the car. I'll be back soon.
Sergeant,
I found Duangjai and Anna, but we missed each other just now.
I'll send you the location.
Please send me reinforcements immediately.
- Anna, Anna's daughter.
- Who are you? Don't chain me.
- Mom, Mom, calm down.
- Let me go, you damn son of a bitch.
- Let me go. I'm going to kill it.
- calm down
- Calm down, Mom.
- Take it easy.
Just a little bit more,
and I will be able to avenge you, my mother.
If that day comes,
I will let you kill that damn beast with your own hands.
You hellish creature!
I'll kill it. I'll kill it.
I will kill it.
Fah.
Don't tell me that all the things you have done,
because you believe your crazy mother.
Who is the reason why my mother is like this?
Both you and mom have to suffer,
isn't it because of that scumbag?
Fah. What are you doing now?
Fah!
Fah! What are you doing?
What else are you going to do, Fah?
Keng
Let's do it before they come for my mom and grandma.
Shit.
What the hell?
What the hell! What is happening now?
Brother, do you have a flat tire?
Yes, I have a flat tire.
Can you change the tire for me?
Five hundred.
Okay.
Do you have any spare one?
I have one in the trunk. Come on.
Here, yours.
This is my last time.
I won't do it anymore.
You don't have to get involved anymore.
You should hurry up and go.
I'll take care of him myself.
Be careful.
Wake up already.
You can't escape anywhere tonight.
You've been using other people's genes for a long time.
Tonight you will make amends.
Shit, what should I do?
Fah, the police are coming.
- Fast, fast.
- Shit.
- What the hell!
- Hurry up, you have to run.
Freeze!
I said freeze! Don't move.
Run away!
- Fast, fast.
- No, I won't!
-Don't move. Raise your hands.
-I told you to go.
I said go!
Place your hands on your head. Don't move!
- I told you to go.
- No!
I won't run away.
Go!
Fah, go!
Keng!
Run away! Quick!
- Keng!
- Don't shoot.
Run away!